Sana Ullah

Document controller/NEOM Approved

Email: Sanaullahyousafzai257@gmail.com

2 +966 50 081 2022 Riyadh, Saudi Arabia

Objective

Highly organized and detail-oriented document controller with 6 years of experience seeking a challenging position in a reputable organization. Possessing excellent communication and analytical skills, I am committed to maintaining accurate documentation management to support efficient workflows and ensure compliance with company and industry standards.

Academic Qualifications

- DAE CIVIL (Diploma Associate Engineer)
- BA (Bachelor in Mass Communication)
- **DIT** (Information Technology)
- Khyber Pukhtonkhwa Trade Testing Board

Competences

- Software programs (Aconex, SharePoint, Power BI, Microsoft Office) Excellent
- Communication and report writing skills,
- Sound knowledge in MS OFFICE tools, Sound knowledge in Aconcex or similar Electronic Document Management system
- Ability to handled documentation independently, Effective time management, including the ability to deal with the conflicting demands in order to meet deadlines
- Professionally committed and have good interpersonal skills
- Fluent in written and spoken English
- Knowledge of evaluation techniques for measuring the effectiveness of the document management infrastructure of the organization

Professional Work Experience

Company: Alfanar Projects

Date : 2024 July to Present

Designation : Document Controller

Project : NEOM Residential Communities (NRC 11, 13, 17, 19 and 26)

Client : NEOM Company

PMC : Bachtel

Company : Abdul Mohsin Al Tamimi

Date : 2022 May to 2024 June

Designation: Document controller

Project: 03-Oxagon Business Community Phase II.

03-OXAGON DESIGN AND BUILD FOR INTERIM WAREHOUSES AT TO.

03-OXAGON TO Warehouses Cold Chain Equipment.

Client : Neom

PMC : Parsons

Company : Sabban Electromechanically contractors

Date : 2020 to 2022 (2 year)

Designation: Document controller

Project : Shalal Jeddah power plant Jeddah KSA

Client : SEC

PMC : DAR KSA

Company : Blue Arc Design & Construction Company

Date : 2018 to 2020 (2 year)

Designation: Document controller

Project : Bahria Town Islamabad

Client : DHA

Responsibilities:

- Organizing and Maintaining Filing System for Murcia Housing Society
- Using ACONEX to organize and distribute documents within a company, Consultant, and clients.

 Upload all project documents to the client database through Primavera Unifier.
- Tracking / Maintaining the record of Incoming & outgoing documents.
- Supporting team in Daily / Weekly / Monthly Reporting.
- Updating the consulting crew and contractor's database.
- Creating a log for the documents to be handed over to the areas managers.
- Sharing the documents at key times to facilitate timely project completion.
- Collaborate with project staff and management, plan, and coordinate meetings.
- Facilitate progressive handover of documents to Operations at agreed completion stages
- Coordinating with the biggest contractors like (SBG, NESMA, ELSEIF, ALFOUZAN, FIRST FIX, MABANI) and consultants (DAR AL-HANDASA, SAUDI DIYAR, Khatib & Alami SAUDI CONSULT).
- Responsible for Material Inspection Report (MIR) by submitting all required documents.
- Field visiting to the projects as required.
- Follow up with the sales engineer & customers and provide all necessary documents like (Warranties, Letters and governmental legal certificates).
- Maintaining the documentation process routine (Printing, Copying, Scanning, Storing & Archiving

 Preparing & Submitting the technical material submittals for the new projects.
- Obtained more than 1000 material approvals in key projects in KSA.

Skills & Expertise

- Aconex.
- Professional Technical Support.
- Microsoft office
- SharePoint.
- Power BI

Languages

- English
- Arabic
- Urdu

Personal Data

Nationality Pakistani
Age 28
Religion Islam
Civil Status Married

I hereby certify that all information given are true and correct to the best of my knowledge and any fraudulent misinterpretation herein made shall be enough grounds for the company to act unfavourably on my application and to be used as a basis of sanction in the event that I am hired.

5/26/24, 3:16 PM Aconex

Nezar Battan NEOM - PROJECTS Final (WF-105944) 4800000824/000 CVS- Document Con... 2:51 PM
WORKFLOW TRANSMITTAL NPR-WTRAN-018146

03 OXAGON

NEOM Industrial City

NEOM Saudi Arabia



MAIL TYPE
Workflow Transmittal

MAIL NUMBER
NPR-WTRAN-018146

REFERENCE NUMBER NPR-WTRAN-018146

Final (WF-105944) 4800000824/000 CVS- Document Controller - Sana Ullah

From Mr Nezar Battan - NEOM - Projects

To (2) Mr Nezar Battan - NEOM - Projects (+1 more...)

Cc (8) Mr 4800000824 AMT DCC - Abdulmohsen Altamimi Contracting Company (+7 more...)

Sent Sunday, 26 May 2024 2:51:08 PM AST (GMT +03:00)

Status N/A

DOCUMENT ATTACHMENTS (1)

(0 s	selected)					
	File	Document No	Revision	Revision Date	Title	Status
	کہ	03-230000-4800000824-AMT- HRM-CVS-000037	01	23/05/2024	4800000824/000 CVS- Document Controller - Sana Ullah	A - Work May Proceed

MESSAGE

Workflow Review History

The attached documents have completed the "4800000824/000 CVS- Document Controller - Sana Ullah" workflow with the following results:

This transmittal was automatically generated.

Doc No	Step	Participant	Review Outcome	Comments
03-230000-4800000824- AMT-HRM-CVS-000037	PMC DCM	N Parsons	B - Incorporate Comments - Proceed	Subject to one month probation period. Neom procedures should be followed throughout the project.

5/26/24, 3:16 PM Aconex

NEOM SPM Final N Battan A - Work May Proceed







DIPLOMA OF ASSOCIATE ENGINEER Civil Revised 2013

	Session Annual 2018			
Certified that Mr/Miss	SANAULLAH			
Son/Daughter of _	NOOR MUHAMMAD			
Registration No.	GCT/SWT/CT/II-S/15-44331			
ď	GOVERNMENT COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY SWAT			
	Sociate Engineer CIVIL REVISED 2013 Khyber Pakhtunkhwa Board of Technical Education, Peshawar in the month 2608 Marks out of 3450 and has been placed in			
	In recognition thereof, this Diploma of Associate Engineer			
is awarded to him/her at	Peshawar on the29Thday ofOctober 2018			

TSECRETARY



Secretary

GOVERNMENT OF KHYBER PAKHTUNKHWA

PESHAWAR PAKISTAN Diploma in information Technology





Serial No. 38541	Session2020-21		Roll No99562
Certified that Mr./Miss/Mrs Sanaullah	<i>S/</i> _	D/W.ONoor Muha	mmad
Registration No. NCA/SWT/DIT/SEP/20/5	Institute _ Noor Computer Ac	ademy Khawaza Khela Swat	*
Has successfully completed the one year	duration course titled "Diplo	oma in Information I	Technology (DIT)" and
passedits examination conducted by Khybe	er Pakhtunkhwa Trade Testing .	Board Peshawar	26-10-2021
He/She obtained 1187 marks out	of1400 Grade	A+ And in recogni	tion thereof this one year
Diploma in Information Technology is awa	rded to him/her.		
on the 25th day of May 2022			
	1		

Allama Ighal Open University

Serial No. A319109

Certified that Mr. / Ms.

SANAULLAH

Son / Daughter of NOOR MUHAMMAD

Registration No: 16NST03592

Roll No: BL410141

having completed the prescribed requirements in semester

SPRING 2021

is awarded the degree of:

Bachelor of Arts Group - Mass Communication

He/She has secured 61 % marks and placed in B grade.

CONTROLLER OF EXAMINATIONS

Result declared on: 21 January 2022

Date of Issue: 9 January 2024

CE-CHANCELLOR